# **Valeria Paulina Lustres**

FullStack Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina (GMT-3) (+549) 1121714493

valeriapaulinalustres@yahoo.com.ar https://linkedin.com/in/valeria-paulina-lustres https://portfolio-kappa-green.vercel.app https://github.com/valeriapaulinalustres

FullStack Developer with 3 years of experience in Design and FrontEnd Development. I work on apps that process large volume of data from backend to get immediate and efficient results, in the Municipality of Moron and Inteligentia. Also, I am a Javascript tutor teacher at Coderhouse. I appreciate learning new technologies opportunities and professional growth.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Inteligentia - Front End React Developer** — February, 2022 - current

• I manage to develop complex views which works with multiple endpoints to configure user's tasks and graphs. Tech stack: React JS, SQL, Dashboards, ApexCharts, Websockets.

# **Coderhouse – Javascript tutor teacher** — June, 2022 - current

• I achieved 90% of the students understanding of complex topics during the complementary classes through didactics designed from the practical activity.

Tech stack: Javascript.

## **TECHO - Front End React Developer** — May, 2022 – January 2023

• I developed complex views of the Frontend that facilitate multiple tasks for users, and I helped in the coordination of the interns, providing support in their tasks and difficulties.

Tech stack: React JS, Javascript, Material UI, Git, Github, Node JS, Express, GSAP, React chart js, GIT.

## Municipality of Moron - Front End React Developer - Backend Node Js — May, 2020 - current

- I reduced 90% the time of processing large volumes of data. I optimized the health worker's daily tasks and helped speed up the implementation of specific actions.
- I designed and developed an app that analyzes data on different diseases in the population and allows authorities to make relevant and timely decisions.

Tech stack: React JS, Javascript, CSS, Typescript, Node JS, Express, GSAP, React chart js, R, Figma, GIT, Dashboards.

# **MAIN PROJECTS**

#### Sweet Expectancy App - <a href="http://dulce-espera.vercel.app">http://dulce-espera.vercel.app</a> - 2022

• It allows physicians to get drug information related to pregnancy from the FDA.

Tech stack: React, Typescript, API REST, Figma.

# **The lupines e-commerce** - <a href="https://ecommerce-reactlustres.vercel.app">https://ecommerce-reactlustres.vercel.app</a> - 2022

• This e-commerce helped the micro-enterprise to raise its sells a 100% during the first month.

Tech stack: React, Javascript, Firebase, CSS.

#### **SKILLS**

**Programming Languages:** Advanced: Javascript; Intermediate: Typescript.

Frameworks Tools: Advanced: React JS, SASS; Intermediate: Node JS, Express JS, Next JS. Basic: Nest Js

Data Base: Intermediate: Mongo DB; Basic: SQL.

**Tools:** Git, Github, Figma, Photoshop, GSAP, Jquery, ApexCharts.

Agile: SCRUM.

Languages: Upper Intermediate: English; Native: Spanish.

# **EDUCATION**

Buenos Aires University - Buenos Aires, Argentine. Medicine, may 2008.

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

React Native - Coderhouse. July, 2023.

Backend - Coderhouse. June, 2023.

Front End React Web Development Career - Coderhouse. May, 2022.

EF SET – B1 Upper Intermediate. March, 2022.